http://www.visitorsinsurance.com/privacy_policy.asp

Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) and Visitors Insurance Click Here to Read More
info@visitorsinsurance.com
+1-847-897-5120
Home(current)
US Citizens Traveling Abroad
Long term int'l Insurance (H1/L1)
Int'l Group Travel Insurance
Specialty Products
Schengen Visa Travel Insurance
Student Insurance(F1/J1 & OPT)
Employee Benefits for IT Companies
Low Cost Group Insurance (H1/B1 Emp)
USA - PPO DOCTOR/HOSPITAL
AZIMUTH (UNITED HEALTHCARE)
IMG (UNITED HEALTHCARE)
PETERSEN INTL (FIRST HEALTH)
SEVEN CORNERS (UNITED HEALTHCARE)
TOKIO MARINE HCC
TRAWICK INTL (FIRST HEALTH)
INTERNATIONAL - PPO DOCTOR/HOSPITAL
IMG (IPA)
SEVEN CORNERS (WELLABROAD)
TOKIO MARINE HCC
TRAWICK INTL (GBG)
TOKIO MARINE HCC
TRAWICK INTL (CBP)
TRAWICK INTL (NATIONWIDE)
Privacy Policy
Insurance Carrier/Underwriters:
Sirius International | AM Best Rating: A "Excellent" | Administrator : International Medical Group (IMG)
GBG Insurance Limited | BBB Rating : Best's Issuer Credit Rating
| Administrator : Trawick International
Lloyd's of London | AM Best Rating : A+ (Superior) Administrator : HCCMIS Travel insurance
Lloyd's of London | AM Best Rating : A+ (Superior) Administrator : Azimuth Risk Solutions
Lloyd's of London |
AM Best Rating : A+ (Superior) Administrator : Seven Corners
CIGNA Insurance-
Carrier/Underwriter : AM Best Rating : A
Premier Assurance Group SPC LTD |
Administrator : Worldwide Expatriate Association (WEA)
Lloyd's of London | AM Best Rating : A+ (Superior) |
Administrator : Peterson International Underwriters
Community Insurance Agency, Inc. (CIA) offers customers a wide range of insurance products, often available online.
CIA maintains a corporate website describing policy options available through our affiliated insurance companies and intermediaries. Thus, we provide a source of one-stop digital shopping for consumers seeking insurance of all kinds, for all purposes.
Protecting Your Privacy
Please be assured that your personal information is safe, distributed neither indiscriminately nor widely across the Internet.
The information provided is used to respond to any questions that you may have presented us with.
Complete Online Security:
Our Promise to You
CIA is a leader in digital security.
Several CIA insurance plans can be accessed and acquired online.
Our secure Web form eliminates the possibility any other firm or individual can access this material.
NO information exchanged over CIA secure-sites can be viewed by anyone else, anywhere on the Internet.
Protecting your confidentiality is the highest priority at CIA
This is our pledge to you:
We have NO contact with other firms' data-gathering processes, nor their mailing lists.
Everything you share with CIA remains exclusively with us; there is NEVER any third party involvement.
In some cases, a security window will appear on your monitor the moment your insurance inquiry enters a safe zone (URL https://).From there, your contact with CIA is protected by the highest degree of Web security for the remainder of the purchase process.
Community Insurance Agency realizes the importance of your personal information, and its potential to generate discomfort or damage should it fall into the wrong hands.
Our security measures set an industry-standard, which guarantees nothing of value to you can be accessed or compromised acquiring insurance from CIA.
To help us serve you better we do keep your contact number, email address and any other information voluntarily provided by you on file. You could ask us to delete/modify any data we may have on you. You may also opt for no further contact from us a dropping us an email or via a phone call.
We may be required to change our privacy policy at any point in time. We would not be sending out any notification. However, any changes to the privacy policy would be updated on this webpage.
Contacting Us About This Website:
Community Insurance Agency™, Inc.
425 HUEHL ROAD - SUITE #22A NORTHBROOK, IL 60062
PHONE:
Do you have any questions we can assist with or need to schedule a call back? We got you covered!
Request a Call Back
We can give you a call back when you are ready to chat.
Please share your details below.
You can call us toll-free at 1-800-344-9540 or 1-847-897-5120
WhatsApp us at
1-847-897-5120
Our email is
info@visitorsinsurance.com
Hours of Operation : 9:00 AM - 5:30 PM CST (Monday – Friday)
